Neha Erasmus African Union High Level Implementation Panel Papers MS207
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1998 -- 2013; MS207.001; 1042 Digital Object(s)
  - Final signed documents, 2010 -- 2013; MS207.001.00220
    - Agreement between The Government of the Republic of Sudan and The Government of South Sudan on Border Security and the Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2011-06-29; MS207.001.00231
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Borderlands; Border security; Boundary disputes; Demilitarized zone; United Nations Interim Security Force for Abyei
    - Provisions on Nationality and the Freedoms of Nationals of the Other State, 2011-07-14; MS207.001.00232
    - Draft Conclusions of the Communications and Transportation Sub-Cluster, 2011-07-14; MS207.001.00233
    - Agreement on Border Monitoring Support Mission between the Government of Sudan and the Government of South Sudan, 2011-07-30; MS207.001.00234
      The agreement requests the UN to endorse the agreement on the Border Monitoring Support Mission with the following additional tasks to the UNISFA mandate: 1)Provide force protection; 2)Provide observers; 3)Provide logistic and air support; 4: Provide Accommodation for national observers.
      Abyei (Sudan); Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Borderlands; Boundaries; Demilitarized zone; United Nations Interim Security Force for Abyei
    - Appendix 1: Sudan Negotiations - Assessment and Way Forward, 2011-08-16; MS207.001.00235
    - Agreement on a Framework for Cooperation on Central Banking Issues between the Republic of the Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan, 2012-09-27; MS207.001.00236
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Banks and banking, Central; Bank of South Sudan; Bank al-Sūdān al-Markazī; Commercial banks; Joint Central Banking Committee (2012: Sudan)
    - Agreement between the Republic of the Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan on Border Issues, 2012-09-27; MS207.001.00237
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Borderlands; Border security; Transhumance; Tribes
    - Agreement between the Republic of the Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan on Certain Economic Matters, 2012-09-27; MS207.001.00238
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Assets and liabilities; Cultural heritage; Archives--Sudan; Reconciliation; Loans--Sudan
    - Framework Agreement to Facilitate Payment of Post Service Benefits between the Republic of the Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan, 2012-09-27; MS207.001.00239
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Public service; Public servants; Pensions; Pensioners; Joint Ministerial Committee on Pensions (2012: Sudan)
    - Agreement on Security Arrangements between the Republic of the Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan, 2012-09-27; MS207.001.00240
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Border security; Demilitarized zone; Borderlands; Joint Border Verification and Monitoring Mission (2012: Sudan)
    - Agreement on Trade and Trade Related Issues between the Republic of the Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan, 2012-09-27; MS207.001.00241
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; International Trade; Trade Policy; Joint Ministerial Committee on Trade Relations (2012: Sudan)
    - Framework Agreement on the Nationals of the Other State and Related Matters between the Government of the Republic of the Sudan and the Government of South Sudan, 2012-09-27; MS207.001.00242
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Aliens; Citizenship; Freedom of movement; Joint High Level Committee (2012: Sudan)
    - Agreement between the Government of the Republic of South Sudan and the Government of the Republic of the Sudan on Oil and Related Economic Matters, 2012-09-27; MS207.001.00243
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Petroleum pipelines--Fees; Transportation--Equipment and supplies--Tariff; Natural resources; Petroleum industry and trade; Borderlands; Reconciliation
    - The Cooperation Agreement between the Republic of the Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan, 2012-09-27; MS207.001.00244
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Interstate relations--Sudan; Boundary disputes; Citizenship; Petroleum industry and trade; Banks and banking, Central; Pensions; Comprehensive Peace Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement, Sudan People's Liberation Army (2005)--Implementation
    - Adoption of Implementation Matrix by the Republic of the Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan, 2013-03-12; MS207.001.00245
      Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Security; Citizenship; Boundary disputes; Trade; Banks and banking, Central; Pensions; Assets and liabilities; Petroleum industry and trade
    - Security, 2010 -- 2012; MS207.001.00246
      - Report on the 9th meeting of the joint Security Cluster post referendum negotiations, 2010-12-07; MS207.001.00247
      - Joint Position paper on border security, 2011-05-30; MS207.001.00248
      - Agreement between the Government of Sudan and the Government of Southern Sudan on Border Security and the Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2011-06-29; MS207.001.00249
        Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Borderlands; Border security; Demilitarized zone; Joint Political and Security Mechanism (2011: Sudan)
      - Agreement on the Border Monitoring Support Mission between the Government of Sudan and the Government of South Sudan, 2011-07-30; MS207.001.00250
        Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Borderlands; Border security; Demilitarized zone; United Nations Interim Security Force for Abyei; Joint Political and Security Mechanism (2011: Sudan)
      - Agreement between the Republic of Sudan and the Republic of South Sudan on Border Monitoring Support Mission, 2011-08-08; MS207.001.00251
        Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Border security; Borderlands; United Nations Interim Security Force for Abyei; Sudan. Armed Forces; Sudan People's Liberation Army; Joint Political and Security Mechanism (2011: Sudan)
      - Decision of the First Joint Political and Security Mechanism, 2011-09-18; MS207.001.00252
        Borderlands; Border security
      - Memorandum of Understanding of Non-Agression and Cooperation between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Governmen of South Sudan, 2012-02-10; MS207.001.00253
        Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Peaceful coexistence; Sovereignty; Interstate relations--Sudan
      - record of decisions meeting of joint political security mechanism, 2012-02-10; MS207.001.00254
      - The Definition of Cessation of Hostilities, 2012-06-23; MS207.001.00255
      - The Establishment of the Ad Hoc Committee, 2012-06-23; MS207.001.00256
      - Agreement on the Border Monitoring Support Mission between the Government of Sudan and the Government of South Sudan, 2011-07-30; MS207.001.00257
      - Implementation Modalities for Security, 2010-09-27; MS207.001.00258
  - Unfiled material, 2011 -- 2012; MS207.001.00259
    - Meeting with Awad Muhammed, 2011-12-05; MS207.001.00260
    - China to send envoy to mediate in Sudan oil row, 2011-12-05; MS207.001.00261
    - Email to AUHIP, 2011-12-11; MS207.001.00262
    - Draft Resolution for the African Union Assembly, January 2012, 2011-12-13; MS207.001.00263
    - Names, 2011-12-14; MS207.001.00264
    - AUHIP Press Release, 2011-12-20; MS207.001.00265
    - AUHIP Press Release, 2011-12-20; MS207.001.00266
    - AUHIP Press Release, 2011-12-20; MS207.001.00267
    - AUHIP Narrative Report, 2012-07-27; MS207.001.00268
    - Religious Extremism is Against Our Culture and Our Interests, 2012-07-27; MS207.001.00269
  - Framework documents, 2007 -- 2013; MS207.001.00270
    - AUHIP Proposals, 2010; MS207.001.00271
      - Economic Chapeau, 2010-10-12; MS207.001.00272
      - Agreement between The Government of the Republic of Sudan and The Government of Southern Sudan Concerning the Petroleum Sector, 2010-12-12; MS207.001.00273
      - Currency Agreement, 2010-12-14; MS207.001.00274
      - Currency Agreement, 2010-12-14; MS207.001.00275
      - Agreement on Border Issues, 2010-12-15; MS207.001.00276
      - D: Specific Commitments on Nationality, Citizenship and Related Issues, 2010-12-16; MS207.001.00277
      - Specific Commitments on Nationality, Citizenship and Related Issues, 2010-12-17; MS207.001.00278
      - Agreement Between the Government of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement on Currency and Banking Issues, 2010-12-17; MS207.001.00279
      - Draft Chapeau of the Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement Concerning the Petroleum Sector, 2010-12-17; MS207.001.00280
      - Draft Chapeau of the Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement Concerning the Petroleum Sector, 2010-12-17; MS207.001.00281
    - Framework drafts, 2010; MS207.001.00282
      - Proposed text on currency, 2010-10-28; MS207.001.00283
      - Proposed Text on Borders, 2010-10-28; MS207.001.00284
      - Assets and Liabilities Draft Proposal, 2010-10-29; MS207.001.00285
      - Water Draft Proposal, 2010-10-29; MS207.001.00286
      - Commitments on Citizenship and Related Issues, 2010-10-29; MS207.001.00287; Afako, Barney
      - Commitments on the Petroleum Sector, 2010-10-29; MS207.001.00288; Afako, Barney
      - Commitments on Blue Nile State, South Kordofan State, and Popular Consultations, 2010-10-29; MS207.001.00289
      - Commitments for Ensuring Mutual Security, 2010-10-30; MS207.001.00290; Afako, Barney
    - Proposals for Frameworks, 2010; MS207.001.00291
      - Agreement on the North/South Border Region, 2010-10-16; MS207.001.00292
      - Agreement on Southern Sudan Referendum and Popular Consultations, 2010-10-16; MS207.001.00293
      - NCP and SPLM Strategic Agreement on their Post Ref Arrangments, 2010-10-18; MS207.001.00294; Shreim, Muin
      - NCP and SPLM Strategic Agreement on their Post Ref Arrangments, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00295; Shreim, Muin
      - AEC suggested language on Article III: Financial, Economic and Natural Resources, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00296
      - NCP and SPLM Strategic Agreement on their Post-CPA Relationship and Guidelines for Post-Referendum Issues, 2010-10-23; MS207.001.00297
      - Rationale: Borders, 2010-10-28; MS207.001.00298
    - Technical work, 2007 -- 2013; MS207.001.00299
      - AUHIP Working Group, 2010; MS207.001.00300
        - AEC / UN/ AUHIP / US Meeting 19 Oct, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00301
        - AUHIP Working Group Meeting 24 October 2010, 2010-10-24; MS207.001.00302
        - AUHIP Mediation Support Technical Working Group 25.10.10, 2010-10-25; MS207.001.00303
        - AUHIP Mediation Support Technical Working Group sub group, 2010-10-25; MS207.001.00304
        - AUHIP Mediation Support Technical Working Group sub group, 2010-10-26; MS207.001.00305
        - AUHIP Team Sub-Group Allocation, 2010-10-26; MS207.001.00306
        - AUHIP Mediation Support Technical Working Group sub group, 2010-11-03; MS207.001.00307
        - Meeting AUHIP Working Group, 2010-11-03; MS207.001.00308
        - Working Group Plenary Meeting 081110, 2010-11-08; MS207.001.00309
      - Borders, 2007 -- 2013; MS207.001.00310
        - Declaration of the African Union Border Programme and its Implementation Modalities as Adopted by the Conference, 2007-06-07; MS207.001.00311
        - Concept Note, 2010-03-22 -- 2010-03-25; MS207.001.00312
        - Borders, 2010-10-26; MS207.001.00313
        - Feb committee agreed border line, 2010-10-28; MS207.001.00314
        - Map 3.1 Abyei, 2010-10-30; MS207.001.00315
        - Notes on Maps for Contested Borderlands, 2010-10-30; MS207.001.00316
        - Ilemi triangle map, 2013-05-06; MS207.001.00317
        - Map 3.6.2, 2013-05-06; MS207.001.00318
      - Citizenship, 2010; MS207.001.00319
        - UN Recommendations on Citizenship Principles in the case of Secession of South Sudan, 2010-10-24; MS207.001.00320
      - Economics, 2010; MS207.001.00321
        - Issue Brief for Addis Ababa Talks: Assets and Liabilities, 2010-10-25; MS207.001.00322
        - Issue Brief for Addis Ababa Talks: Currency, 2010-10-25; MS207.001.00323
        - Issue Brief for Addis Ababa Talks: Water, 2010-10-25; MS207.001.00324
      - Legal, 2010; MS207.001.00325
        - Legal Issues, 2010-09-17; MS207.001.00326
      - Oil, 2010; MS207.001.00327
        - Post-Referendum Arrangements for Sudan's Oil Industry or How to Separate Siamese Twins, 2010-10; MS207.001.00328
      - Transnational Political Parties, 2010; MS207.001.00329
        - Transnational Parties Meeting, 2010-11-02; MS207.001.00330
      - Technical Experts, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00331; Mozersky, David
      - Experts Already Engaged and Requested by the Parties, 2010-10-20; MS207.001.00332
      - Proposed Research Agenda, 2010-12-11; MS207.001.00333
      - Proposed Research Agenda, 2010-12-11; MS207.001.00334; Erasmus, Neha
    - NCP Strategic strategic agreement on their post-CPA relationship and guidelines for post referendum issues, 2010-10-20; MS207.001.00335
    - General Commitments by the Parties and Presidency towards Referendum and Post-Referendum Periods - draft, 2010-10-23; MS207.001.00336
    - Second Meeting of the Sudan Consultative Forum, 2010-10-25; MS207.001.00337
  - Friends, 2010; MS207.001.00338
    - Concept Note: "Friends of the Panel" Meeting, 2010-08-25; MS207.001.00339
    - Budget, 2010-10-07; MS207.001.00340
    - Friends Meeting Contacts & Logistics, 2010-10-07; MS207.001.00341
  - Heglig War, 2012; MS207.001.00342
    - Remarks by Ambassador Susan E. Rice, U.S. Permanent Representative to the United Nations, at the Security Council Stakeout, 2012-04-11; MS207.001.00343
    - Statement by Victoria Nuland, Spokesperon, 2012-04-11; MS207.001.00344
    - UK Statement 12 April 2012, 2012-04-12; MS207.001.00345
    - Press Release on Sudan and South Sudan, 2012-04-16; MS207.001.00346
    - On the Conflict between Sudan and South Sudan, 2012-04-16; MS207.001.00347
    - On the Conflict between Sudan and South Sudan statement to the security council, 2012-04-16; MS207.001.00348
    - On the Conflict between Sudan and South Sudan statement to the security council, 2012-04-16; MS207.001.00349
    - On the Conflict between Sudan and South Sudan statement to the security council, 2012-04-17; MS207.001.00350
    - On the Situation in Sudan and South Sudan - communique, 2012-04-23; MS207.001.00351
    - Plan of Action for Implementation of AU PSC Roadmap, 2012-04-24; MS207.001.00352
    - Draft Timeline for implementation of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union (AU), security decisions taken at the 319th meeting held at ministerial level, 2012-04-26; MS207.001.00353
    - Draft Timeline for implementation of the Peace and Security Council of the African Union (AU), security decisions taken at the 319th meeting held at ministerial level, 2012-04-26; MS207.001.00354
    - Plan of Action for Implementation of AU PSC Roadmap, 2012-04-26; MS207.001.00355
    - AUHIP draft letter GoS, 2012-04-27; MS207.001.00356
    - AUHIP draft letter to Abdel gader, 2012-04-27; MS207.001.00357
    - AUHIP draft letter Amum, 2012-04-27; MS207.001.00358
    - AUHIP draft letter Nyuong, 2012-04-27; MS207.001.00359
    - Urgent Task to Ensure the Mutual Security of the Republics of Sudan and South Sudan, 2012-05-09; MS207.001.00360
    - Urgent Tasks to Ensure the Mutual Security of the Republics of Sudan and South Sudan, 2012-05-10; MS207.001.00361
    - Centreline Map for SDBZ: Explanatory Note, 2012-05-13; MS207.001.00362
    - Remarks on Dr. Ghazi Salah el Din's Article, 2012-05-15; MS207.001.00363
    - Situation in Sudan, 2012-05-16; MS207.001.00364
    - Ping Draft letter to UNSG, 2012-05-19; MS207.001.00365
  - HR, 2012; MS207.001.00366
    - Draft ToRs for Jerome Tubiana, 2012-03-17; MS207.001.00367
  - Inter-Governmental Authority on Development, Transition Support Unit, 2011 -- 2013; MS207.001.00368
    - Tentative Plan for Negotiations July - September 2011, 2011-07-14; MS207.001.00369
    - Abdul Mohammed Letter to IGAD Extension, 2011-11-06; MS207.001.00370
    - Abdul Mohammed Letter to IGAD, 2011-12-20; MS207.001.00371
    - Abdul Mohammed letter to IGAD Jan Negotiations, 2012-01-11; MS207.001.00372
    - Letter to IGAD, 2012-01-12; MS207.001.00373
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Negotiations Support, 2012-01-18; MS207.001.00374
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Negotiations Support, 2012-01-21; MS207.001.00375
    - Abdul Mohammed Letter to IGAD Recruitment, 2012-02-05; MS207.001.00376
    - Abdul Mohammed Recruitment Request, 2012-02-05; MS207.001.00377
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Feb Negotiations IGADTSU, 2012-02-05; MS207.001.00378
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Border Nationality Ext IGADTSU, 2012-02-15; MS207.001.00379
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Border Nationality Ext IGADTSU, 2012-02-15; MS207.001.00380
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Extentions Jan Negotiations IGADTSU, 2012-02-15; MS207.001.00381
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Ext IGADTSU, 2012-03-16; MS207.001.00382
    - Abdul Mohammed Request May Negotiations IGADTSU, 2012-05-24; MS207.001.00383
    - Abdul Mohammed Request JPSM IGADTSU, 2012-06-02; MS207.001.00384
    - Abdul Mohammed Request AJOC IGADTSU, 2012-06-05; MS207.001.00385
    - AUHIP letter Goodluck Jonathan Nigeria, 2012-06-05; MS207.001.00386
    - Abdul Mohammed Request June Negotiations IGADTSU, 2012-06-15; MS207.001.00387
    - Abdul Mohammed Request July Negotiations IGADTSU, 2012-07-21; MS207.001.00388
    - Abdul Mohammed Request IGADTSU Extension, 2012-07-28; MS207.001.00389
    - Letter visa Laura, 2012-08-02; MS207.001.00390
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Sep Negotiations IGADTSU, 2012-09-01; MS207.001.00391
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Sep Negotiations 2 IGADTSU, 2012-09-06; MS207.001.00392
    - Abdul Mohammed Letter to IGAD Extension, 2012-11-23; MS207.001.00393
    - Abdul Mohammed Request Dec IGADTSU, 2012-12-10; MS207.001.00394
    - Abdul Mohammed request IGADTSU, 2013-01-05; MS207.001.00395
    - Abdul Mohammed request IGAD TSU, 2013-04-06; MS207.001.00396
    - Abdul Mohammed request IGAD TSU, 2013-04-16; MS207.001.00397
    - Abdul Mohammed request IGADTSU, 2013-04-16; MS207.001.00398
  - Implementation, 2012 -- 2013; MS207.001.00399
    - Abyei, 2013; MS207.001.00400
      - AUHIP letter Hassan Al-Bashir Abyei Temp Arrangements, 2013-03-21; MS207.001.00401
    - Joint Technical Committee on Pensions, 2013; MS207.001.00402
      - A letter to Mbeki from Idris Abdel Gadir, 2013-03-24; MS207.001.00403
      - A letter to Amum from Idris Abdel Gadir, 2013-03-24; MS207.001.00404
    - Oil, 2013; MS207.001.00405
      - Government of Sudan Oil Resumption Letters, 2013; MS207.001.00406
        - A letter to Stephen Dau from Awad al Jazz, 2013-03-18; MS207.001.00407
        - A letter from Awad al Jazz to Stephen Dau, 2013-03-18; MS207.001.00408
        - A letter to Mbeki from Abdel Gadir, 2013-03-21; MS207.001.00409
        - A letter from Awad al Jazz to Gnpoc, 2013-03-21; MS207.001.00410
        - A letter to Awad al Jazz from Stephen Dau, 2013-03-19; MS207.001.00411
        - A letter from Awad Mohammed to Stephen Dau, 2013-03-17; MS207.001.00412
        - Abdul Mohammed letter AUC PMC Chair Lamamra, 2013-03-20; MS207.001.00413
        - Abdul Mohammed letter AUC PMC Chair Lamamra, 2013-03-20; MS207.001.00414
        - Abdul Mohammed letter GoS RSS PMC Chair Idris Abdel Gadir, 2013-03-20; MS207.001.00415
    - Republic of South Sudan Joint Border Commission, 2012 -- 2013; MS207.001.00416
      - A letter to Amum from Lueth, 2012-01-11; MS207.001.00417
      - Formation of Joint border commission, 2012-05-14; MS207.001.00418
      - Replacement of two members of the joint border commission, 2012-05-24; MS207.001.00419
      - The appointment of the joint demarcation committee, 2012-05-24; MS207.001.00420
      - Trade Committees, 2013-03-26; MS207.001.00421
    - Security, 2013; MS207.001.00422
      - A letter to Tesfamariam from Abdulerahim Hussein, 2013-03-17; MS207.001.00423
      - A letter to Tesfamariam from Abdulerahim Hussein, 2013-03-17; MS207.001.00424
    - Adoption of the Implementation Matrix, 2013-03-12; MS207.001.00425
    - A letter to Koryom from Badr Abbas, 2013-03-18; MS207.001.00426
    - A letter to Amum from Idris Abdel Gadir, 2013-03-19; MS207.001.00427
    - Letter from Dhieu Dau to Awad al Jazz, 2013-03-20; MS207.001.00428
    - A letter to Mbeki from Idris Abdel Gadir, 2013-03-21; MS207.001.00429
    - A letter to Amum from Idris Abdel Gadir, 2013-03-21; MS207.001.00430
    - Timing Matrix d2, 2013-03-21; MS207.001.00431
    - A letter to Mbeki from Idris Abdel Gadir, 2013-03-24; MS207.001.00432
    - Committee Formation, 2013-03-26; MS207.001.00433
    - A letter to Mbeki from Idris Abdel Gadir, 2013-03-26; MS207.001.00434
    - A letter to Amum from Idris Abdel Gadir, 2013-03-26; MS207.001.00435
    - Timing Matrix Monitoring, 2013-03-26; MS207.001.00436
  - Joint Technical Secretariat, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00437
    - March 24, 2011 meeting, MS207.001.00438
      - Currency, 2011; MS207.001.00439
        - Currency, MS207.001.00440
        - Session 1 Currency, 2011-03-01; MS207.001.00441
        - Currency sub-group meeting, 2 March 2011, 2011-03-02; MS207.001.00442
        - Currency session, 2011-03-02; MS207.001.00443
        - Currency sub-group meeting, 3 March 2011, 2011-03-03; MS207.001.00444
        - Currency session 2, 2011-03-03; MS207.001.00445
        - Currency sub-group meeting, 4 March 2011, 2011-03-04; MS207.001.00446
        - Currency session 3, 2011-03-04; MS207.001.00447
        - Agreed Minutes of the Subgroup on Currency and Banking, 2011-03-05; MS207.001.00448
      - Debt, 2011; MS207.001.00449
        - Debt, MS207.001.00450
        - Joint NCP-SPLM Debt Relief Request Letter FINAL, 2011-03; MS207.001.00451
        - Debre Zeit Round Facilitation Record of 2 March Discussions, 2011-03-03; MS207.001.00452
        - Debre Zeit RoundFacilitation Record of 3 March Discussions, 2011-03-04; MS207.001.00453
        - Debre Zeit Round Summary of Decisions - Sub-cluster on Assets and Liabilities, 2011-03-13; MS207.001.00454
        - Debre Zeit Round Final Facilitation Record of 1-4 March Discussions, 2011-03-23; MS207.001.00455
      - List of outstanding agreed actions, 2011-03-07; MS207.001.00456
      - AU HIP/AEC/ Joint Technical Secretariat MOU monitoring meeting: 22 February 2011, 2011-03-08; MS207.001.00457
      - Follow up steps for the Joint Technical Secretariat, 2011-03-23; MS207.001.00458
      - JTS Meeting, 2011-03-24; MS207.001.00459
      - Economic Negotiations - Logistics and Arrangements, 2011-03-25; MS207.001.00460
      - Security Issues for JTS, 2011-03-25; MS207.001.00461
      - Oil, MS207.001.00462
    - JTS draft budget, 2010-09-14; MS207.001.00463
    - Memorandum of Understanding between the Lead Negotiation Panel on the Post Referendum Negotiations for Sudan, 2010-09-16; MS207.001.00464
    - JTS / AEC / AU Meeting 011210, 2010-12-01; MS207.001.00465
    - JTS / AEC / AU Meeting 011210, 2010-12-01; MS207.001.00466
    - JTS / AEC / AU Meeting 011210, 2010-12-01; MS207.001.00467